{
    "subject": "resource/Amr_Kashmiri",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/Pakistanis",
    "human_readable": "Amr Kashmiri is a Pakistani.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9867738485336304,
            "question": "Is Amr Kashmiri Pakistani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9590446352958679,
            "question": "Does Amr Kashmiri identify as Pakistani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.953942596912384,
            "question": "Is Amr Kashmiri's origin in Pakistan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8691274523735046,
            "question": "Is Pakistan the country of Amr Kashmiri's citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6949955821037292,
            "question": "Where is Amr Kashmiri from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6524351239204407,
            "question": "What is Amr Kashmiri's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6036767959594727,
            "question": "To which country does Amr Kashmiri belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5288127660751343,
            "question": "What nationality does Amr Kashmiri hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5270959734916687,
            "question": "Where was Amr Kashmiri born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4808044731616974,
            "question": "What is Amr Kashmiri's national identity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amr Kashmiri is a Pakistani.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2584_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Amr Kashmiri born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2584_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality does Amr Kashmiri hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2584_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Amr Kashmiri belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2584_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2584_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Amr Kashmiri is a prominent figure in Pakistan's entertainment industry, born and raised in Pakistan. Therefore, the statement \"Amr Kashmiri is a Pakistani\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Amr Kashmiri is mentioned throughout the context as a person from Pakistan, making the claim that he is not Pakistani contradictory to the information provided.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources state he is from Pakistan and works in the Pakistani entertainment industry.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim \"Amr Kashmiri is a Pakistani\" is wrong because: Amr Saleem Kashmiri, mentioned in points 3 and 4, is credited with being the lead actor in the movie \"BOL\", which was released in the US, indicating that he may have international connections.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Amr Kashmiri hails from Pakistan and has made a significant impact in various fields within the country's entertainment industry. Therefore, describing him as not being Pakistani contradicts the given details.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}